const myQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Which team won the first ODI WCï¼Ÿ",
        answers: {
            a: "West Indies",
            b: "India",
            c: "England",
            d: "Australia"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a",
        correctAnswerResult: "West Indies"
    },
    {
        question: "Which team won the recent T20 World Cup",
        answers: {
            a:  "India",
            b:  "Newzemand" ,
            c:  "Australia",
            d:  "South Africa"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c",
        correctAnswerResult: "Australia"
    },
    {
        question: "In which year India Premier League was started",
        answers: {
            a: "2007",
            b: "2010",
            c: "2009",
            d: "2008"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d",
        correctAnswerResult: "2008"
    },
    {
        question: " Who was player of the tournament of 1996 Odi cricket World Cup ",
        answers: {
            a: "Md Azharuddin(India)",
            b: "Sanath Jayasuriya(Srilanka)",
            c: "Wasim Akram(Pakistan)",
            d: "Ricky Ponying(Austalia)"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b",
        correctAnswerResult: "Sanath Jayasuriya(Srilanka)"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the recent winner of male ICC Player of the decade(2011-2020)",
        answers: {
            a: "Steve Smith(Australia)",
            b: "Virat Kohli(India)",
            c: "Kane Williamson (Newzeland) ",
            d: "Ab devilliers(South Africa)"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b",
        correctAnswerResult: "Virat Kohli(India)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the most successful team in Big Bash League",
        answers: {
            a: "Peth Scorshers",
            b: "Sydney Sixers",
            c: "Stydey Thunders",
            d: "Both a and b"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d",
        correctAnswerResult: "Both Perth Scorshers and Sydney Sixers have won 3 times therefore option d is correct"
    },
    {
        question: "Which stadium is known as Home of Cricket",
        answers: {
            a: "Lords(England)",
            b: "Gabba(Australia)",
            c: "Eden Garden(India)",
            d: "The Oval(England7)"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a",
        correctAnswerResult: "Lords(England)"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the most successful team in Indian Premier League(IPL)",
        answers: {
            a: "Mumbai Indians",
            b: "Kolkata Knight Riders",
            c: "Royal Challengers Bangalore",
            d: "Sunrisers Hyderabad"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a",
        correctAnswerResult: "Mumbai Indians"
    },
    {
        question: " Which players has scored most runs in Caribbean Premier League history",
        answers: {
            a: "Chris Gayle ",
            b: "Dinesh Ramdin ",
            c: "Lendl Simmons ",
            d: "Marlon Samuels"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c",
        correctAnswerResult: "Lendl Simons "
    },
    {
        question: "Who has taken most number of wickets in World Test Championship 2019-21 Season",
        answers: {
            a: "Trent Boult(Newzeland)",
            b: "Jasprit Bumrah(India)",
            c: "Pat Cummins(Australia)",
            d: "Ravinchandran Ashwin(India)"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d",
        correctAnswerResult: "Ravichandran Ashwin"
    },
    

];